

Applicant for:

Senior Web Frontend ~1,800\$

Dr.JOY 18 March 2021

Tran Thi Hương Trang

☑ tranthihuongtrang2209@gmail.com

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Tran Thi Hương Trang skipped the cover letter.



Tran Thi Huong Trang

QA - Tester

Hello there, My name's Tran Thi Huong Trang.

I'm 32 year old. I have more than one year of experience working at Fsoft and three years working at Sun*. I'm a careful and hard-working peson. I'm eager to learn new things and i like dealing with difficult problems and challenged issues.





Software

1 = beginner, 2 = basic, 3 = intermediate, 4 = advanced, 5 = proficient.

MySQL	1	2	3	4	5
SQL-Server	1	2	3	4	5
Adobe Indesign	1	2	3	4	5
Adobe Lightroom	1	2	3	4	5
Eclipse	1	2	3	4	5
Netbean	1	2	3	4	5
Redmine	1	2	3	4	5
SVN	1	2	3	4	5



Working Skills

Highly understanding about Test Process, Test Techniques
Master the software development process (includes: requirement, analysis, implement and test
Good research ability
Highly skill in using defect management tools
Install and deploy test enviroiment

Work Experiences

Q

07/2020 - present

Thang Long Academy

Marketing

- Designing the logo and banner
- Website design and development for company profile on fanpage and websites.
- Designing video.
- Photography



04/2019 - 12/2019

QA - Sun*

Project description:

- Website connects employers and influences to adventise products for businesss.
- Team site: 20
- Responsibilities:
- + Study SRS
- · + Create, review testcace, test data
- + Execute Test



09/2016 - 08/2018

QA - Frangia (Sun*)

- A project consists of many projects of one customer.
- + Designing website for schools.
- + Perform version ups for old sites
- Team site: 20
- Responsibilities:
- + Study SRS
- + Asign task to members
- + Create, review testcace, test data
- + Execute Test



03/2016 - 08/2016

Tester - FPT Software

Project description:

- The software used for the tablet to handle the express
- Team site: 400
- Responsibilities:
- + Study SRS
- + Create, review all testcace insite, test data
- + Execute Test



05/2015 - 03/2016

Tester - FPT Software

Project description:

- Development management system:
- + duty-free shops in Japan airports
- + bus tickets for the bus system in Japan
- Team site: 25
- Responsibilities:
- + Study SRS
- + Create, review all testcace insite, test data
- + Execute Test



Summary of Project:

Project type: Project base

Domain:

- + Logictic: 1
- + Ecommerce: 2
- + Education: 2

Program type:

- Mobile: 1
- Web: 5
- API: 2
- Batch: 2
- Window application: 1



Education

2010 - 2013

HA NOI APTECH

APTECH CERTIFIED COMPUTER PROFESSIONAL

2007 - 2010 QUANG NINH EDUCATION COLLEGE

CHEMISTRY TEACHER



Languages

English :basic (writing & reading)



Skills and Abilities

- Logical thinking and problem solving .
- · Computer programming
- Conflict resolution
- Seft Confidence
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Positive Attitude



Achievements

ISTQB foundation level ICAgile Certified